just finished my half an hour of
meditation I'm feeling very peaceful and
well doing meditation I had I felt many
thoughts many thoughts that's all
meditation is is sitting and breathing
and relaxing my body and letting the
thoughts flow through and I've been
trying to make these videos and explain
my global cooperative and I'm still
that's still a mission I'm on I'm still
figuring out how to best explain this
amazing solution that is coming through
me so that the people who are first
supposed to come on board keep them on
board but also in doing so I've also
been watching other people's YouTube
videos and the ones that I feel drawn to
I mean believe me they're better editing
and everything than I am but the big
difference I think is that they talk
about themselves and are vulnerable and
people can see them and so maybe I'm not
supposed to be talking about my idea and
I'm supposed to be talking about me
because if that's what I'm drawn to and
it's something I've been struggling with
grappling with it's been an issue is
this idea that when you're attracted to
someone or with someone to folks and
emotion in you it's because of something
in yourself so if you hate someone and
they're annoying you it's because you
have that thing that they're annoying
you based on and if you're attracted to
someone then the same thing right if you
find someone's beauty and essence
amazing then it's because you're seeing
a piece of you in them so there were
swings both ways and realizing over the
last year that I do in fact like women
that I'm not as straight I'm not
straight at all it's like zero
straightest to me but I thought a year
ago that I was straight that's what
identified us and figuring out who I'm
attracted to and then I'm attractive to
more masculine women or in drugs
as women and trying to figure out okay
to wait does that mean that I want to be
like that or am i attracted to that and
holding those two things at the same
time like I do
I love women with short hair but I don't
know if I want short hair even though I
wear my hair in a ponytail all the time
and I get annoyed with my long hair I
also strongly I'm attached to it that I
know one of my one of the times I always
say that I don't care what I look like
one of the times that was clearly
evident that's not quite as true as I
thought it was was before my first brain
surgery when I didn't understand how
much of my hair was gonna be shaved it
was my biggest worry going into it I was
like shave as little as possible I just
want my hair and they shaved a small
patch back here and it slowly grew in
and after my second brain surgery Wow
two years ago today today's the 31st
isn't it of August two years ago today
and they had to do it was my scars
across here and so they shaved more of
it and after that I had this weird urge
that I wanted to shave my entire head
and I put it off a few months like hey
wait wait maybe on that one and the urge
is definitely gone but the difference
between being attracted to someone or
something that's something I'm trying to
do something be attracted to someone and
realizing how much of that attraction is
that I want to be like them and how much
is know I want to be me and whatever
that is and I can still be attracted to
that and it's weird because I never felt
that way as a heterosexual woman
attracted to men I never had the thought
like maybe and but realizing how in my
life that was absolutely true that I was
attracted to well men in male clothing
and always was annoyed that they got to
you they're fat a sense of fashion sense
is easier thrown a t-shirt and jeans
they're one like a button-up shirt and
you're good to go and if I was a man and
I could I would be able to dress better
and I only just had the Epiphany like
six seven months ago like wait and I
don't wouldn't call it dressing better
but
I'm allowed I'm allowed to wear men's
what we would call men's clothing and
you'll find it it and so yeah it's
something I'm constantly struggling with
and so I think I'm gonna share more
about that side of me not just that but
all of it by realizing I'm queer and the
and all of the like beauty and pain and
craziness the coast with that as well as
my my health issues my disability past
and present being a single mom being a
single mom by choice like I think that
people are gonna more resonate with my
truth my inner truth and what I want and
don't want is followers and I wanted to
be able to talk about my global
cooperative but finding a way to be
vulnerable and showing who I truly am
brings people on board in a different
way and as I'm figuring out how to also
explain it in written form and I'm
trying to write a book an e-book that I
can give away and so yeah balancing that
figuring out what I'm gonna be talking
about because I don't want to stop these
hundred day videos I think they're a
powerful point for me even though no
one's watch them but it's coming from
that point I'm going to talk about
things that feel more vulnerable to me
so yeah today is day 14 which is a
number since that's my birthday number
and it feels alright I missed yesterday
day which would have been day 14 but
today feels perfect because it's the
31st it's two years since my brain surge
or my last my last and hopefully final
final final brain surgery and it's a
shift it's the end of a month beginning
of the school year yeah I just feel
feels right today and so I am going to
use this channel to be more vulnerable
and share myself thank you